myhuckleberry.com 2014-06-17

# MyHuckleberry Privacy Policy

The following information is to help users and visitors (collectively "Users" or "You") understand how we collect, use, disseminate, and safeguard the information You provide to us while accessing and using our MyHuckleberry.com software, services, the website at www.myhuckleberry.com (the "Website"), and any other websites and services as may be added from time to time (collectively, "Service"). This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the MyHuckleberry.com End User License Agreement ("License Agreement"). Your use of the Service and any personal information You provide on or through the Service remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our License Agreement. 

1\. Information Collection 

MyHuckleberry.com collects certain information to enable you to take full advantage of our offerings when you register at our site, order products or services, participate in our contests, surveys, promotions, or activities, or otherwise communicate with us. If you choose, you can visit MyHuckleberry.com without providing us with any information about yourself. MyHuckleberry.com collects both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information from users of its Website. 

You may provide certain personally identifiable information to MyHuckleberry.com, Inc. directly, such as your first and last name, telephone number, address, and email address (collectively, "Personally Identifiable Information") when choosing to register, purchase, or use Services, participating in promotions or surveys, or subscribing to any newsletters or other distribution lists. 

When you register with MyHuckleberry.com, we require you to give us contact information (such as your name, email address, or physical address). We may require additional information for specific promotions or contests run on our Website. 

We may use the customer contact information we collect to connect you with a service provider, and to send you, if you so choose, information about our company, newsletters, promotional materials, and information from the service provider network. 

We may also use the information we collect, in combination with outside records, to notify you about important changes to the Website, new MyHuckleberry.com, services and products, and special offers and information we think you'll find valuable. We may send you information in conjunction with third-party partners that we think is relevant to your interests. 

We may use information gathered at the time of purchase to process your order, to enable the provider to fulfill your order, and to notify you of your order status. A customer care representative or service provider may contact you in order to fulfill a service you purchased or to provide information you requested. 

Any graphics, text, files, or any other content submitted, transmitted, or uploaded to the public areas of the Website or through the Website by Users ("User Submissions"), or other material that You make accessible to others directly, becomes published and public information that is not protected as "Personally Identifiable Information." Be aware that if your User Submissions includes personal information, such as your name and email address, other Users will have access to it and it will not be protected Personally Identifiable Information. 

When You visit our Website and use our Service, we may collect and store that information, including the following: 

a. Cookies. When You visit the Website, we may send one or more cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer that identifies your web browser. You can set your web browser to refuse cookies; however, this may limit the functionality our Website can provide to You. 

b. Log Files. Your web browser automatically reports log file information each time You view a web page. When You register with or use the Service, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever You visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your IP address, browser type and language, number of clicks, domain names of websites visited, pages viewed, and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time. 

c. Clear Gifs. When You use the Service, we may use clear gifs (also known as “web beacons”) to collect information. 

Information collected through clear gifs and cookies, and log file information is largely non-personally identifiable information because such information is not collected or used in such a way that an individual User can be identified, for example, by name or email address (collectively, "Non-Personally Identifiable Information"). 

For example, Non-Personally Identifiable Information may be the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, the referring site from which you came (like a partner site), and the domain name of your Internet service provider (like America Online or EarthLink). 

We use the Non-Personally Identifiable Information that we collect in the aggregate to improve the design and content of our site. We also use this information to analyze site usage. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

2\. Use of Information 

Collected information is used to operate, maintain, and provide to You the features and functionality of the Service. Any information or User Submissions that You submit to the Website (including on discussion boards or forums, in blogs, messages and chat areas, and other areas) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by other Users, who may forward this information or User Submissions to other websites or people, making it available to the general public and, therefore, it will not be protected Personally Identifiable Information. 

We may use your Personally Identifiable Information for billing, administrative purposes, such as notifying You of major changes in Service, news, and for other customer service purposes. You hereby consent to our use of your email address to send you such information. 

We may use collected information to: (a) remember information so that You will not have to re-enter it during your current or subsequent visits to the Website; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; (e) track User Submissions, and status in any promotions, sweepstakes, and contests; (f) diagnose or fix technology problems; (g) access your information after You sign in; (h) market our Service to advertisers and other third parties; and (i) to improve the quality and design of the Service and to create new features by storing, tracking, and analyzing your preferences and trends. 

3\. When We Disclose Information 

We may provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or others, including to service providers for the purposes identified in the preceding Section 2. If we provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information to such third party, their use of that Non-Personally Identifiable Information shall be governed by their privacy policy, not MyHuckleberry.com’s Privacy Policy. 

To process your requests for products or services, we will need to share some of the personally identifiable information you provided (like contact information and information about particular service needs) with service providers in the provider network. 

If you choose to receive promotions, newsletters, and/or other types of correspondence from us, the correspondence that you receive will originate from MyHuckleberry.com, Inc., or the provider network, and your personally identifiable information will continue to be solely maintained by MyHuckleberry.com. 

If you registered with MyHuckleberry.com. through a third-party website or if you registered with a third-party website through MyHuckleberry.com, we may need to report certain information to that website, as is necessary. 

If you come to MyHuckleberry.com via a co-branded partner and transact business with us, the information you provide may be collected and used by MyHuckleberry.com as well as by the co-branded partner from which you came. MyHuckleberry.com is not responsible for the use that the co-branded partner makes with this information. 

To help you identify when you are on MyHuckleberry.com website, we place our logo in the upper left corner to indicate that you are within our website. 

MyHuckleberry.com may be obligated to disclose personally identifiable information to law enforcement or agencies, even though such agencies may not comply with the terms of our privacy policy. MyHuckleberry.com will disclose information to such agencies in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena, or a law enforcement agency's request. 

MyHuckleberry.com may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, partners, service providers, or to the press. Aggregate statistics contain only non-personally identifiable information. 

In order to describe our Service to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties we may disclose aggregate user information. We share Non-Personally Identifiable Information (such as anonymous use data) with third parties to assist them in understanding our Service, including Users' use of our Service and the success of promotions. 

We may release collected information if required to do so by law, or if we believe that such action is appropriate to comply with state and federal laws or respond to a court order, law enforcement request or demand, subpoena, or search warrant. We may share collected information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including but not limited to, fraud, potential threats to public safety or the physical safety of any person, violations of our License Agreement or Privacy Policy, or as otherwise permitted by law. 

We also reserve the right to disclose collected information that MyHuckleberry.com, Inc. believes is appropriate or necessary to enforce our License Agreement or Privacy Policy, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our Service, and to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of MyHuckleberry.com our Users or others. 

4\. Service Providers 

Service may be used in conjunction with services provided through a variety of third parties, such as Google; and MyHuckleberry.com may allow other third parties to serve advertisements through the Website or Service. The use of User Submissions and other information provided by You to such third parties is governed by their privacy policies, not our Privacy Policy. MyHuckleberry.com is not responsible for third party privacy policies or their compliance with such policies. 

5\. Choices 

You may update or correct your Personally Identifiable Information at any time using the Software or by sending us an email. If You or MyHuckleberry.com intend to delete any User Submissions provided by You, we cannot guarantee that your User Submissions will be completely removed from all User devices or from their web pages, nor that other Users will not misuse any content that You supply. In addition the other Users may have already copied and forwarded your User Submissions to others, making recovery impossible. 

6\. Data Security 

When you place orders or access your account information, we use a secure server. The secure server software, SSL (Secure Sockets Layer), encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, digital certificates protect all of the customer transactional data we collect against unauthorized access. MyHuckleberry.com, Inc. uses VeriSign, one of the most established issuers of digital certificates, to issue digital certificates. Additionally, we use firewall security and limit data access to protect your personally identifiable information. 

We have put in place procedures to provide data security of our servers. We take precautions to protect your Personally Identifiable Information and other data from loss, misuse or alteration and to safeguard and secure the data You provide. While we strive to protect such information after it arrives at our servers, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that is being transmitted over the Internet. As a result, You provide such information at your own risk. 

7\. Children's Privacy 

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information submitted by persons under 18 years of age. If You are under 18 years of age, then please do not submit any information to the Website at any time or in any manner. 

8\. International Users 

Our Service servers are hosted in the United States and our Service is intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If You are accessing the servers from outside the United States, the laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure may differ from United States laws. Be advised that through your continued use of the Service, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy and our License Agreement, You are transferring your personal information to the United States and You hereby consent to that transfer and you agree that any information you submit will be subject to United States privacy laws regardless of where you are physically located. 

9\. Merger or Bankruptcy 

In the event that we acquire, are acquired by, or merge with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign all collected information as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy or similar situation, we may not be able to control how your information is treated, transferred, or used. 

10\. How to Update or Change Your Preferences 

MyHuckleberry.com may send communications, promotional information, and/or newsletters to our registrants. You can choose to not receive communications from us. We provide the following options for reviewing and updating the personally identifiable information that we collect and maintain, including options for communications, news, and special offers. 

To review and update your choices, please use our contact form. 

11\. Privacy Policy Changes and Updates 

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting. Any changes will be reflected by the effective date at the beginning of the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any current revisions.
